# Nicolas Riabosapko

## **Customer Support Specialist**

nikolasrralonso@gmail.com (+351) 935-169-488

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Customer Support analyst with 5 years of experience, team player with people skills and a friendly positive attitude, motivated to perform at peak levels, exceptional communication and writing skills, strong ability to multitask, prioritize, and manage time effectively. Comfortable working in English, Portuguese and Spanish.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Porto - Portugal

Manpower Group, Porto - Technical Support Advisor (Concentrix project)

April 2018 - Present

- Provide Technical support to end-customers in the EMEA region, mostly focused on the UK market, focusing on investigating, troubleshooting and resolving customer issues in a clear, concise and straightforward manner
- Demonstrate professionalism and courtesy at all times, maintaining customer satisfaction as a priority.
- Manage call-flow and responding to all technical or non-technical related questions, always going the extra mile by providing as many information and assistance without compromising data privacy and confidentiality
- Assist on management and training of new advisors, sharing procedural knowledge, technical troubleshooting strategies and best practices

Conduent Brasil, São paulo - Senior Technical Support Advisor

July 2014 - July 2016

- Assist customers in issues that demands an extra attention and a more detailed investigation, gathering log files and working side-by-side with engineering team towards a resolution
- Manage wide variety of customer service and administrative tasks
- Interpret and analyze data and creating strategies for a resolution, adding the successful cases for analysis and update of internal and external knowledge base
- Provide functional guidance, training, support and assistance to junior advisors, and staff from different departments within the company

#### **EDUCATION**

Full-Stack Web Developer- FLAG - Porto

sep 2020 - apr 2021

**Electrotechnics** - Instituto Edison - Sao Paulo

jun 2014 - jun 2016